ipad-3-news.com 2012-05-18

# iPad 3 News Disclaimer and Privacy Policy – iPad 3 News on Release Date and Rumors

This website is not owned by, licensed by or a subsidiary of Apple Computer, Inc.  **Apple iPad**  are trademarks of Apple Computer, Inc., registered in the U.S. and other countries. The content of this website is not supplied or reviewed by Apple Computer, Inc.

If any information on this website is inappropriate or violates or infringes any of your copyright protection let us know and appropriate action will be taken as soon as possible. All the information available on this site is for informational purposes only.

All articles, images, logos and trademarks in this site are property of their respective owners. Comments are property of their posters and  _iPad-3-news.com_. The information on the blog may be changed without notice and is not guaranteed to be complete, correct or up to date.

Links to external sources are provided solely as a courtesy to our blog visitors. We are not responsible for and do not endorse or warrant in any way any materials, information, goods or services available through such linked sites or any privacy or other practices of such sites.

All data and information provided on this site about the iPad 3 are for informational purposes only.  _iPad-3-news.com_  makes no representations as to accuracy, completeness, suitability, or validity of any information on this site and will not be liable for any errors, omissions, or delays in this information or any losses, injuries, or damages arising from its display or use.

## Our Privacy Policy

(last update: October 2011)

### Information we gather

The following information is gathered from our website visitors:  
IP address

### How we use the information we gather

We use the information to enhance your visitor experience.

### The people that are given access to this information

Your personal information is accessible by server administrators.

### The security measures we have in place to protect your personal information

To safeguard your personal information, we security measures in place at the host level.

### Our use of cookies

Our website makes use of cookies which are small digital files that are stored in your web browser that enable us to track your return visits to our website.

Your browser settings may allow you to block these cookies, but we recommend you have them enabled to help us personalise your experience of our website.

Additionally, 3rd party advertisers on our site may use cookies for tracking purposes.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on their visit to sites they visit on the Internet.

Website visitors may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
